<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">OMGUW Reader</string>
    <string name="service_name">OMGUW Reader New Post Checker</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="action_top">Go To Top</string>
    <string name="section_omg">OMG</string>
    <string name="section_mc">MC</string>
    <string name="section_oh">OH</string>
    <string name="section_ask">ASK</string>
    <string name="title_activity_post_comments">Comments</string>
    <string name="posts_empty">Unable to load posts. Are you connected to the internet?</string>
    <string name="comments_empty">Unable to load comments. Are you connected to the internet?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">This app was created by Roman Tymchyk.\n\nOMGUW Reader is an unofficial app for OMGUW, and as such is not affiliated with, endorsed, or sponsored by OMGUW (or University of Waterloo). Its function is for entertainment purposes only. I am not responsible for any content displayed. Use at your own risk.\n\nMany thanks to the people at OMGUW for maintaining the site.</string>
  	<string name="help">If you have any questions about OMGUW Reader, please do not hesistate to contact me via e-mail (rtymchyk@gmail.com)</string>
  	<string name="network_error">Uh Oh! There was a problem fetching the data. Check your internet connection and try again later.</string>
  	<string name="license_one">The MIT License (MIT)\n\nCopyright (&#169;) 2013 Aidan Follestad\n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>
  	<string name="license_three">Copyright Google\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
  	<string name="license_two">Copyright 2013 readyState Software Limited\n\nCopyright 2012 Google Inc\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
  	<string name="menu_share_entry">Share</string>
  	<string name="pref_post_checker">Post Checker</string>
  	
  	<string name="changelog_full_title">Change Log</string>
    <string name="changelog_title">What\'s New</string>
    <string name="changelog_ok_button">Ok</string>
    <string name="changelog_show_full">More</string>
</resources>
